Here's a quick method to test. If your
application back in is stateless or not,
fire up your client and log
in and send few requests to
your back end.
After that, stop sending requests, go to the
back and restart the process or the
Entire Computer. Where the backend
application lives. Wait for your
back, end to come back up and
running and then go back to the
client and then send
another request.
If that request a new request
succeeds, that means your application back in
is completely stateless. If
that request fails, that means your
application. Depends on some sort of a
state that knows no longer there.
Typical stateless applications or protocols is
HTTP or DNS
while websockets or TCP, or
example of a stateful protocols.
While HGTV does use TCP HTTP
at that application layer if that
TCP connection is distort. It just
creates another one.